<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Carlos Zoido</title>
    <link>https://czoido.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Carlos Zoido</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://czoido.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Some of my projects</title>
      <link>https://czoido.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 09:56:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://czoido.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>These are some project I have done during these years.
Projection mapping software and Multi-projector correction software In 2018 I decided to make a completely new application to calibrate Multi-Projector systems based on what I had learned during my Ph.D. I also reused some of the algorithms from that software to make an automatic calibration system for Projection Mapping. Here are some videos of the results of that development. I planned to distribute some free demos of these applications once complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://czoido.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 09:56:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://czoido.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Automatic correction method for panoramic multi-projector displays DYNA (September 2013) Abstract In this paper we present an easy and novel method to calibrate a panoramic multi-projector display system. These kinds of displays have a wide range of applications in fields such as simulation, entertainment, marketing and data visualization.
Our correction method uses a commercial off-the-shelf camera that rotates around its vertical axis in order to cover the entire screen. Light structured patterns are projected on this screen in order to establish the transformation that relates the camera to each projector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://czoido.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 09:37:06 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://czoido.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can DM me on Twitter or just write me an e-mail to carloszoido [at] gmail [dot] com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://czoido.github.io/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 09:03:14 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://czoido.github.io/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>The presentation Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Carlos. A Software Engineer from Madrid. This blog is just an excuse to keep track of some things I do.
Since I was a child, I have felt a non-ending curiosity for many different subjects. That thirst of knowledge is what has mainly driven my personal, academic and professional career and was the cause that made me study Industrial Engineering to learn what made things work. After finishing my studies, I started working as a C++ Software Developer in a Research Centre at the Polytechnic University of Madrid.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
